export const Questions = [
    {
        id:'quest-1',
        question:'How much should I invest in Boosting?',
        answer:`Boosting guarantees that you only pay for the clicks that your listing gets. The cost of each campaign
        depends on your budget. The higher your budget, the more clicks the campaign will try to deliver to your
        listing.
        Marketoo suggests you to purchase from $0.1 - $10/ per click`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-2',
        question:'Will I have discount if I invest more into Boosting?',
        answer:`Yes! It is a Pay As You Go Scheme which allows you to optimise your Boosting ads accordingly.
        $10 > Now 8
        $20 > Now $15
        $50 (10% off) > Now $40
        $80 (15% off) >Now $68
        $150 (20% off) >Now $120
        $300 (25% off) >Now $225
        $500 (30% off) > Now$350`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-3',
        question:'Why should I pay for higher clicks?',
        answer:`Higher clicks correlate with a more prominent position when sellers share same Ad score and same Product
        Quality score, thereby delivering clicks faster for a successful campaign and competing with other sellers
        in the category in a given period of time. `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-4',
        question:'If I do not pay for higher clicks, does this mean my Boosting ads will perform poorly?',
        answer:`No. Your Boosting listing will be shown in relevant search and browse results. We will still aim to deliver
        100% of your daily budget. Your Boosting performance will not be impacted. Higher Clicks is built for the
        serious sellers who urgently want more exposure and clicks in a specific given period of the time. `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-5',
        question:'What if all other sellers pay for the same clicks? Who will be prioritised?',
        answer:`If all other sellers are paying for the same clicks, then all of their listings will be prioritised based on the
        highest Product Quality score followed by the highest Ad Score. `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-6',
        question:'How do I put my listing into Boosting?',
        answer:` 1. Select a listing from your profile and tap on ‘Promote’
        2. Look for Boosting and tap “x HKD /click”
        3. Customise your Boosting campaign with a daily budget by setting the target number of clicks, and
       keywords. You pay then proceed to confirm payment by tapping on “Boost Now”.
       Track the clicks and progress of your Boosting campaign through My Performance in the “Ads Management”`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-7',
        question:'How do I Track the clicks and progress of your Boosting campaign?',
        answer:`Track the clicks and progress of your Boosting campaign through My Performance in the “Ads Management”`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-8',
        question:'How do I pay for my Boosting?',
        answer:`Ads features like Boosting can be purchased via our web using a credit card. `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-9',
        question:'How to calculate Product Quality score?',
        answer:`Your Product Quality score is calculated by (Conversation Rate + Clicks) x 5.
        Maximum Product Quality is 10.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-10',
        question:'What is the Maximum Product Quality?',
        answer:`Maximum Product Quality is 10.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-11',
        question:'Is Boosting subject to other considerations?',
        answer:"No."
    },
    {
        id:'quest-12',
        question:'How do you calculate Ads score?',
        answer:`Ad Score = Max. CPC Bid x Listing Quality Score`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-13',
        question:'What if I am still unsure of the calculation?',
        answer:`If you are still unsure of the calculation, you may refer to our suggested bid value`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-14',
        question:'How long will my listing stay in Boosting?',
        answer:`Your listing will stay in Boosting for as long as you set your campaign duration to be (3–30 days) and will
        pause for the day once you’ve reached your daily budget (or targeted number of clicks per day).
        
        Marking your listing as “Sold”, “Out Of Stock”, “Deleted” or changing its category will stop your
        Boosting immediately. Reserved listing's promotion will be paused for a maximum 24 hours. Within 24h, relist the listing will bring back the promotion automatically. Over 24h, then it will be stopped. Re-listing
        will not cost any surcharge within the duration you paid for. `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-15',
        question:'Where can I find my boosting?',
        answer:`The appearance of boosted listings is determined by its relevance for each user and the number of clicks
        and priority you’ve set. It’s customised for every user and hence, you may not see it in your own search
        results. To check the performance of your Boosting campaign, simply view your performance under “Ads
        Management”`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-16',
        question:'What happens if the item is “Sold”, “Out Of Stock” or “Deleted” or changing its category while it is in Boosting?',
        answer:`Once you mark your listing as sold, out of stock or deleted or changing its category while it is in Boosting,
        your campaign will be paused for up to 24 hours. If you unreserve your listing within the next 24 hours,
        your listing will be placed back in Boosting! `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-17',
        question:'How do I know if my listing is promoted with Boosting?',
        answer:`You can track the progress of your Boosting campaign through My Performance under “Ads Management”.
        When a user browses a category or search result page, they don’t always tap into all the listings that they
        see. When they scroll past a listing, it’s counted as an impression. When they tap into the listing to view
        more details, it’s counted as a click
        A user has to tap into your Boosting listing for us to count it as a click. On top of that, each click will be
        unique; if the same user taps into your listing twice on the same day, it will only be counted as 1 click. 
        `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-18',
        question:'Does Boosting guarantee a sale?',
        answer:`Boosting provides your listings with more visibility. However, we cannot guarantee that a Boosting will lead
        to a like, chat or offer. To make sure you get the most out of Boosting, use them on good-quality listings.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-19',
        question:'Can I convert un-used money back into my credit card?',
        answer:`Yes, un-used coins can be converted back into money once purchased.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-20',
        question:'Can I use a custom keyword to target?',
        answer:`We all know that buyers search what they want to browse and purchase. As a seller, you would like to put
        certain keywords in the listing title and description with the hope of being shown in the prominent
        position for the highly intended keyword. Keyword targeting assures your hope into reality. You can simply
        select the keywords you want to target at a specific price and your listing will be shown in the keyword
        search result! `
    },
    {
        id:'quest-21',
        question:'If I choose one keyword for the targeting, does this mean my Boosting ads will only show for that keyword? How it will be charged?',
        answer:`No. Keyword targeting will only give an extra boost to your listing for that keyword search. Your Boosting
        performance for organic search will not be impacted. Keyword targeting is built for sellers who want more
        exposure and clicks for a specific keyword. We charge $0.1 bid value per keyword.`
    },
    {
        id:'quest-22',
        question:'Can I add a custom keyword to target?',
        answer:`No. The list of the keywords will be automatically generated based on your listing information, and it will
        be ordered by our recommendation. You can only choose any keyword within the recommended list of
        keywords.`
    }
]